let quiz   =[
    {question: "Which is the only even prime number? ",
option:[
    "zero",
    "1",
    "2",
    "4",

],
answer:3, 
},

{
    question: "What is the square root of 289?" ,
option:[
    17,
    14,
    12,
    16,


],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "Is zero a position or a negative",
option:[
    "Negative",
    "Positive",
    "Both Negative and Positive",
    "Nove of these",

],
answer:4, 
},
{question: "75% of Rs. 1200 is equal to______.",
option:[
    400,
    600,
    900,
    550,

],
answer:3, 
},

{
    question: "How many years together make decade?",
option:[
    12,
    10,
    50,
    100,

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "How many positive integers are there in between -5 and 5?",
option:[
    5,
    0,
    1,
    4,

],
answer:4, 
},
{
    question: "What is the measurement of a straight angle?",
option:[
    "45 degree",
    "90 degree",
    "180 degree",
    "360 degree",

],
answer : 3, 
},
{
    question: "The Roman numeral M stands for ____?" ,
option:[
    1000,
    100,
    10,
    50,


],
answer:1, 
},
{
    question: "Which number is neither prime nor composite?",
option:[
    0,
    1,
    2,
    3,

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "What is the square of 50?",
option:[
    25000,
    250,
    25,
    2500,

],
answer:4, 
},
{
    question: "How many decimal points can there be in a number?",
option:[
    2,
    "So Many",
    1,
    0,

],
answer : 3, 
},
{
    question: "If Cost Price is Rs.85 and Selling Price is 105, then What is the profit?",
option:[
    20,
    30,
    25,
    10,

],
answer:1, 
},
{
    question: "A mathematics test was given to a class of 40 students. 4/5 of the students gave all correct answers. How many students made some mistake? ",
option:[
    32,
    16,
    8,
    0,

],
answer : 3, 
},
{
    question: "What is the place value of 5 in 7569423",
option:[
    500000,
    50000,
    5000,
    500,

],
answer:1, 
},
{
    question: "How many hours are there in 90 minutes?",
option:[
    "1.5 hours",
    "2.5 hours",
    "1 hours",
    "2 hours",

],
answer:1, 
}]